Hey, I'm Ann Myrick, and I'm going to talk to you about how to jazz up your laundry room.
Laundry rooms are small...usually small, and, of course, it's more of a little working room, but it's fun to make it your own.
It's fun to make it fun.
So you can bring in fun wallpaper.
I'm a decorator, and I work with what people have, but a lot of times, the laundry room is a place that we'll do something really fun.
Since it's little, you can do a fun technique or a fun paper because you're not going to need very much.
I'm not a big paper person, but I do think it's fun to put a wild, fun paper in a laundry room or a fun color.
This laundry room has a great color in it, but it's not really a fun color.
It's the color that goes with the rest of the house, and you can just break the mold and do whatever makes you kind of energetic -- a bright apple green, an orange.
You could put stripes in it, you could put fun pictures.
Go on and decorate it like you would even a powder room or a small room, but have fun with it.
You also want to deck it out where it has the things you need -- cute baskets, maybe a bar going across that has...that you can hang clothes and hang towels on.
Really organize it, make it very clean because you have your clean clothes in there.
But really make it fun.
I've taken laundry rooms and put a real bright, fun coat of orange in a room, and it just gives you energy and it's really zippy.
So this is Ann Myrick, and have fun with your laundry room.